kazor.com 2005-12-13

# Privacy Statement kazor.com

## 

## Privacy Statement for kazor.com

## The World's Community Newspaper

Ybor City Telco has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: kazor.com The World's Community Newspaper. 

**PLEASE NOTE** The Ybor City Telco or its parent company American Marketing Management and Motivation Services Inc, make NO INDEPENDENT INVESTIGATION of the products, services or properties or of the people placing advertisements on this site. We accept all ads that art submitted with the appropriate fee. Accordingly, we CAN NOT ACCEPT ANY RESPONSIBILITY  for the direct or consequential damages arising from ANY ads (including want ads)  that are placed. However. **"WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO LIMIT EDIT OR REJECT ANY OR ALL COPY WHICH IN THE OPINION OF THE PUBLISHERS   CONFLICTS WITH OUR OBJECTIVES**" .

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

This site contains links to other sites. **kazor.com The World's Community Newspaper** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. ** MAKE SURE that you explain the other data that you mentioned you collect here. ** 

** DON'T FORGET to include a description of the other services that you have that collect information here. 

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. (*Please elaborate on the security measures that you have in place.) 

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [sales@kazor.com](mailto:sales@kazor.com)
  2. You can visit the following URL: http://kazor.com/administration.htm/
  3. You can send mail to the following postal address: 
  4. 410 South Ware Blvd.  
Suite 619-F   
Tampa, FL 33619 
  5. You can call the following telephone number: 813 626 5261

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [sales@kazor.com](mailto:sales@kazor.com)
  2. visit http://kazor.com/administration.htm/
  3. send mail to the following postal address: 
  4. 410 South Ware Blvd.  
Suite 619-F   
Tampa, FL 33619 
  5. call the following telephone number: 813 626 5261

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

Chris Kazor  Ybor City Telco  410 South Ware Blvd.  
Suite 619-F   
Tampa, FL 33619  [sales@kazor.com](mailto:sales@kazor.com)
